[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Robert De Niro plays a timid and artistic NYC police detective. Bill Murray plays the criminal boss and Uma Thurman is a call girl De Niros character falls for.", "correct_answer": "Mad Dog and Glory", "incorrect_answers": ["A Police Story", "Paths to Glory", "Turner and Hooch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Michael when the heads of the families are killed in the film The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "A baptism", "incorrect_answers": ["His fathers funeral", "He is killing Mo Green", "His office"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What team became the English Premier League champion in the 2006-2007 season?", "correct_answer": "Manchester United", "incorrect_answers": ["Liverpool", "Arsenal", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of dish is the popular South African meal called Melktert?", "correct_answer": "Dessert", "incorrect_answers": ["Soup", "Stew", "Salad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What politician did Scarlett Johansson campaign for in the 2004 US presidential election?", "correct_answer": "John Kerry", "incorrect_answers": ["Barack Obama", "Dick Cheney", "George Bush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Triceratops is the official State Dinosaur of which state?", "correct_answer": "Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Utah", "Oregon", "Nevada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character on Star Wars said No blasters! No blasters!?", "correct_answer": "Bartender", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Evazan", "Greedo", "Stormtrooper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Darwin had a passion for this popular hobby, which was introduced to him by his cousin William Darwin Fox.", "correct_answer": "Collecting beetles", "incorrect_answers": ["Collecting herbs", "Painting", "Fowling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The USA leads\u201d the world in per capita consumption of water. Which country is second?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "India", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What member of the cast of the 2008 movie Vicky Cristina Barcelona won their first Academy Award for their performance in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Penelope Cruz", "incorrect_answers": ["Rebecca Hall", "Javier Bardem", "Scarlett Johansson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following colors is an example of a Tyndall effect color?", "correct_answer": "The blue of the human iris", "incorrect_answers": ["The red of the red apple", "All of these", "The color of the human skin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Historians often attribute Napoleons defeat at Waterloo to which of these reasons?", "correct_answer": "All of these reasons", "incorrect_answers": ["Napoleon had hemorrhoids", "Wellington took a big risk and it paid off", "Marshall Ney had special ties to Wellington and intentionally did not turn Wellingtons right flank"]}]